{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Which of those immunoglobulin classes is mainly found in external secretions?", "opta": "Ig A", "optb": "Ig D", "optc": "Ig M", "optd": "IgE", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Cleavage of an IgG molecule by a specific protease can produce", "opta": "an antigen-binding site and two constant regions", "optb": "two heavy chain-light chain dimers", "optc": "an inactive mixture of oligopeptides", "optd": "two Fab fragments and one Fc fragment", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Papain digest IgG into", "opta": "two Fab fragments and one Fc fragment", "optb": "three Fab fragments and two Fc fragments", "optc": "two Fab fragments and two Fc fragments", "optd": "three Fab fragments and three Fc fragments", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Antibodies can be used", "opta": "for the localization of proteins in the cell", "optb": "for protein purification", "optc": "to catalyze chemical reactions", "optd": "all of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Type A blood", "opta": "can be used to donate to type AB individuals", "optb": "can be used to donate to type B individuals", "optc": "contains type B antigens on the surface of red blood cells", "optd": "can always be used to donate to an Rh+ individual", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following are responsible for immune specificity?", "opta": "Antigens", "optb": "Antibodies", "optc": "T lymphocytes", "optd": "Macrophage", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which species lack immunoglobulin light chains?", "opta": "Camels", "optb": "Humans", "optc": "cows", "optd": "Buffalo", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Monoclonal refers to", "opta": "a single clone of antibody-producing cells", "optb": "all the antibody molecules which are identical", "optc": "the binding with same antigenic site with identical binding affinities", "optd": "all of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "\u03b2-Lymphocytes are often called simply", "opta": "B cells", "optb": "T cells", "optc": "T Lymphocytes", "optd": "none of these", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "IgE provides", "opta": "immunity against some parasites", "optb": "complement killings of the cells and phagocytosis", "optc": "secretions in the body", "optd": "all of the above", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Fab fragment has", "opta": "one antigen binding site", "optb": "two antigen binding site", "optc": "one antibody binding site", "optd": "two antibody binding site", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The main function of antibodies is to", "opta": "kill all the foreign bodies", "optb": "generate antigens, thus conferring immunization", "optc": "protect the circulatory system", "optd": "chemically combine with the antigen which induces it, inactivate the antigen and protect the body from disease", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Alum is an effective adjuvant because it", "opta": "disaggregates the antigen.", "optb": "is immunogenic for stem cells", "optc": "is immunogenic for T cells", "optd": "slows the release of antigen", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A secondary antibody is an antibody that", "opta": "has been used in prior experiments", "optb": "is synthetically produced", "optc": "binds to another antibody", "optd": "is produced in boostered animals", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The immunoglobulin fold is", "opta": "found only in IgG molecules", "optb": "a \u03b2-barrel composed of a three- and a four-stranded antiparallel \u03b2-sheet", "optc": "both (a) and (b)", "optd": "found six times in the IgG molecule", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Antibodies of the IgG class", "opta": "consist of four subunits", "optb": "are glycoproteins", "optc": "are secreted into the bloodstream", "optd": "all of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Each IgA antibody molecule consists of", "opta": "four polypeptide chain and has two antigen binding site", "optb": "two polypeptide chain and has one antigen binding site", "optc": "three polypeptide chain and has two antigen binding site", "optd": "two polypeptide chain and has two antigen binding site", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Antibodies in the human immune system can identify approximately 108 different molecules Which one of the following is correct?", "opta": "This diversity is generated from 108 different immunoglobin genes", "optb": "Many of these molecules are self-antigens", "optc": "Most of these antibodies recognize proteins", "optd": "Most of these antibodies recognize small organic molecules", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Monoclonal antibodies were first produced by", "opta": "Georges Kohler and Cesar Milstein", "optb": "Sarkar and Sommer", "optc": "Selman Waksman", "optd": "Edward Jenner and Louis Pasteur", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A polyclonal antibody response", "opta": "is produced only in response to polymeric antigens", "optb": "is produced by several B cells recognizing different  pitopes on the same antigen", "optc": "occurs during the lag phase of the immune response", "optd": "violates clonal selection", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Structures of anti-PCP antibody shows that the tight binding of PCP to the antibody is primarily due to", "opta": "hydrophobic forces", "optb": "electrostatic forces.", "optc": "Van der Waals forces.", "optd": "none of these", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Antigenic determinants bind to which portions of an antibody?", "opta": "Variable regions", "optb": "Constant regions", "optc": "Only light chains", "optd": "Only heavy chains", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The humoral immune response relies on the production of soluble proteins called", "opta": "antibodies", "optb": "macromolecules", "optc": "lymphocytes", "optd": "none of these", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The human IgG class of antibodies is divided into", "opta": "five IgG classes", "optb": "two IgG classes", "optc": "three IgG classes", "optd": "four IgG classes", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}